Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Shell Oil, 1932-1943; 44
  - Other Programming, 1932-1943; 97
    - Shellane--Commercials, 1941 May-Aug. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shellane--Commercials, 1941 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 181)
    - Spot announcements, 1933-1937 (Film-reel 101)
    - Spot announcements, 1937 (Film-reel 110)
      Legal OK's WSYR Syracuse N.Y.
    - Spotlight on Sports--Commercials, 1943 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 202)
    - Sunset Valley Barn Dance--Commercials, 1942 Apr.-July (Film-reel 202)
    - X-100--Commercials, 1941 May-June (Film-reel 181)
    - X-100--Speaking of Speed commercials, 1941 Apr. 26 (Film-reel 181)
  - Shell Chateau, 1935-1936; 98
    - 1935 Apr.-Nov. (Film-reel 111)
    - 1935 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 113)
    - 1936 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 113)
    - 1936 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 114)
  - Shell Information Show--Five Dollar Fact, 1940-1941; 99
    - 1940 July-Sept. (Film-reel 180)
    - 1941 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 180)
    - 1941 Aug. (Film-reel 181)
- Smaller Accounts, 1929-1955; 45
  - Actin--Boston only, 1931 Dec.-1932 Mar. (Film-reel 10)
  - Alexander Wollcott, 1930 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 11)
  - Allsweet--The Garry Moore Show television, 1955 Jan.-June (Film-reel 1001)
  - American magazine, 1931 (Film-reel 32)
  - Anacine--Army and Navy award program--Life for the Wounded, 1943 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 201)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries, 1931-1932 (Film-reel 11)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries--Nordic Fish, WWSW, 1931 Dec.-1932 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
  - Aunt Jemima, 1929-1932 (Film-reel 11)
  - Bank of America--California Carry On, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 201)
  - Bank of America--Sunday Night Salute, 1944 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 234)
  - Black Horse Ale (Canada)--Commercials, 1938 (Film-reel 133)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield--Advancing Human Frontier television, 1952 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 910)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield--Bill Leonard News--Six O'Clock Report, television, 1955 Feb.-May (Film-reel 1001)
    Some missing
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield--It Seems Like Yesterday television, 1954 (Film-reel 990)
  - Brater's Powder--Commercials, 1940 Sept. (Film-reel 171)
  - Brewing Industry Foundation--Maine spots 31-43, 1943 June 16 (Film-reel 204)
  - British Columbia Packers Association (Toronto)--, 1930 Oct. (Film-reel 10)
  - British-American Oil--Band Wagon (Toronto office), 1942 Feb. (Film-reel 171)
  - Burry Biscuit Co., 1938 (Film-reel 33)
  - Burry Biscuit Co.--Commercials, 1938 July-Sept. (Film-reel 150)
    Incomplete
  - California Wines--Commercials, 1940 Oct. (Film-reel 174)
    In Italian with translations
  - Canadian Marconi Program, 1930 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 10)
  - CeCo dealer program, 1930 (Film-reel 12)
  - CeCo dealer program, 1930 (Film-reel 13)
  - Chateau Haut Briou wine--Broadcast, 1933 (Film-reel 149)
  - Chun King--The Garry Moore Show television, 1955 (Film-reel 1001)
  - Chun King--The Garry Moore Show television, 1956 (Film-reel 1003)
    Episodes missing
  - Clover Leaf salmon, 1931 (Film-reel 32)
  - Colman's mustard--Spot announcements, 1939 (Film-reel 139)
  - Colman's mustard--Spot announcements (WTIC, WLS, WEEI, WSR, WEBC, KSTP, WGY, KDKA, WJAR), 1937 (Film-reel 139)
  - Colman's mustard--Spot announcements--Martha Deane, 1935-1937 (Film-reel 139)
  - Committee to Defend Americans By Aiding the Allies--Spot announcements, 1941 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 170)
  - Corona--How to Write, undated (Film-reel 11)
  - Cosmopolitan magazine--Commercials, 1941 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 170)
  - Current list of radio programs in London, 1937 (Film-reel 342)
    London Office
  - Davey Tree Surgeons--Davey Tree Hour, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 10)
  - E.R. Squibb--Commercials, 1947 June-Dec. (Film-reel 360)
  - Edgar Bergen pictures and press notices, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 342)
  - Enders Razors, 1936 (Film-reel 33)
  - Florida Citrus Exchange, 1935 (Film-reel 33)
  - Foremost Dairies, 1930 Apr.-June (Film-reel 12)
  - General Electric--Radio program, 1941 (Film-reel 171)
  - Graham-Paige, 1937 (Film-reel 33)
  - Gruen--Gruen Guild Radio Program, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 11)
  - Guinness Stout--Commercials, 1941 Jan. (Film-reel 170)
  - Hammond Organ--Hammond Organ Hour, 1937 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 33)
  - Hathaway Bakeries, 1934-1935 (Film-reel 13)
  - Horlick's--Horlick's Picture Show, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 342)
    London Office; programs 163-164
  - International Police--Jitters in Geneva (by Welbourn Kelley) audition, 1945 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 361)
  - Irving Trust--Spot announcements, 1946 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 306)
  - IVC Pearls--IVC Pearls Homemakers Hour, 1930 (Film-reel 11)
  - J.C. Penney, 1937 (Film-reel 33)
  - J.P. French Co.--The World of Mr. Sweeney television, 1955 Jan.-June (Film-reel 1001)
  - Kathleen Norris --Wendell Willkie campaign, 1940 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 35)
  - Kops Brothers (corsets), 1934-1935 (Film-reel 12)
  - Luden's Cough Drops, 1940 Nov. 29 (Film-reel 182)
  - Maine Sardines, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 10)
  - Maine Sardines, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 11)
  - Martini & Rossi (vermouth), 1941 May-June (Film-reel 171)
  - N.Y. State Republican Committee--Commercials, 1941 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 171)
  - Nash Motors, 1934-1937 (Film-reel 12)
  - Nash Motors--Commercials, 1934 (Film-reel 243)
  - Nash Motors--Grace Moore and Vincent Lopez, 1937 May-June (Film-reel 343)
  - National Spelling Bee, 1935 (Film-reel 33)
  - National Spelling Bee--Chase & Sanborn, 1937 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 33)
  - National Spelling Bee--Fleischmann's Yeast, 1936 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 33)
  - Nemoflex, 1931 Mar.-May (Film-reel 10)
  - Northern Trust--The Northerners #788, 1946 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 308)
  - Old Witch--Old Witch radio program, 1929-1930 (Film-reel 13)
  - Oren Root--Campaign Issues, 1949 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 717)
  - Pan American World Airways--Nights in Latin America, 1950 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 736)
  - Pan American World Airways--Nights in Latin America, 1951 Jan.-June (Film-reel 795)
  - Parker Pen--Information Please, 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 308)
  - Parker Pen--Information Please, 1947 Jan.-June (Film-reel 361)
    No broadcast Mar. 5
  - Penick Starch--Commercials, 1942 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 171)
  - People's Drug Co.--Commercials, 1941 Feb. (Film-reel 171)
  - Peters Shoes, 1931 (Film-reel 32)
  - Pharma-Craft--Fresh deodorant spots, 1946 May 17 (Film-reel 308)
  - Proposal for Government Messages on Commercial Network Programs, 1940 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 174)
  - Pyrex, 1930; 1933 (Film-reel 32)
  - R.T. French Co.--French's mustard commercials, 1934; 1938-1939 (Film-reel 133)
  - R.T. French Co.--Instant Potatoes commercials, 1947 May-1948 Apr. (Film-reel 418)
  - Rand McNally & Co., 1930 (Film-reel 32)
  - Rayve Home Permanent--Junior Miss, 1950 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 736)
  - Rayve Home Permanent--Junior Miss, 1950 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 737)
  - Rayve Home Permanent--Winner Take All auditions, 1949 Jan. (Film-reel 717)
  - Reader's Digest--Commercials, 1946 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 305)
  - Reader's Digest--Selecciones (Spanish edition), 1945 July 31 (Film-reel 278)
  - Reckitt's USA Ltd., 1930-1931 (Film-reel 10)
  - Rice's Homemade Bread--Vass Family, 1941 Apr. 25 (Film-reel 171)
  - Richman Brothers Program, 1932 Mar.-June (Film-reel 10)
  - Royal Gelatine--Commercials--Montana, 1941 Oct. (Film-reel 171)
  - S.W. Straus & Co.--Raltenborn edits the news, undated (Film-reel 13)
  - S.W. Straus & Co.--Scripts, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 13)
  - Safeway Stores--Commercials, 1942 (Film-reel 343)
  - Savings Bank, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 33)
  - Scott Paper/Wine Advisory Board--Diane Lucas Cooking show, 1949 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 717)
  - Sharp & Dohme (Hexylresorcinol)--Dr. Howard W. Haggard, 1932 Dec.-1933 May (Film-reel 133)
  - Sherwin-Williams--Metropolitan Opera audition, 1940 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 174)
  - Simmons, 1931; 1937 (Film-reel 32)
  - Skinner Organ, 1930 (Film-reel 32)
  - Skol--Skat spots, 1945 Mar.-May (Film-reel 279)
  - Sterno Canned Heat--Spot announcements, 1941 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 179)
  - Tested Products Laboratories, Inc. (Placidan), 1934 (Film-reel 32)
  - U.S. Brewers' Foundation--Commercials, 1946 Aug. 21 (Film-reel 305)
  - U.S. Government, Citizens Food Committee--Who's for Who in America special broadcast, 1947 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 361)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha Paint Co., 1934 (Film-reel 33)
  - U.S. Marine Corps--Commercials, 1941 Dec. (Film-reel 170)
  - United Hospital Fund--Edgar Bergen, Kate Smith, etc., 1944 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 215)
  - Vogue Fashion Program, 1931 Apr.-Oct. (Film-reel 10)
  - War Manpower Commission--Woman Power, 1944 May (Film-reel 215)
  - Warner Bros.--Out of the Fog scripts and commercials, 1941 May (Film-reel 170)
  - Warner Bros.--Sergeant York commercials, 1941 June-Aug. (Film-reel 170)
  - Wartime Conference--Boys Clubs of America--Herbert Hoover, Lt. Gen. Thomas Holcomb, USMC, 1943 May (Film-reel 201)
  - Weco Products--Dr. West Celebrity Night, 1936 Apr.-May (Film-reel 343)
  - Wendell L. Willkie--Republican campaign, 1940 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 35)
  - Western Union--Easter telegrams auditions, 1948 Mar. (Film-reel 416)
  - Western Union--Mother's Day auditions, 1948 Apr. (Film-reel 416)
  - Widlar Products/Standard Brands--CW Brand coffee--WTAM, WWJ, 1932 (Film-reel 133)
  - Widlar Products/Standard Brands--CW Brand coffee--WTAM, WWJ, 1937 (Film-reel 134)
  - Woman Power--Dramatized spots 1-12, 1943 Mar. (Film-reel 204)
  - Women's National Republican Club, 1947 Sept.; 1948 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 417)
  - Zenith Foundation--Scientific Investigation of Telepathy and Other Unexplored Powers of the Human Mind presented by Zenith Radio, 1938 (Film-reel 33)
- Standard Brands, 1928-1956; 46
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1929-1947; 100
    - Abbott & Costello, 1941 Apr. (Film-reel 202)
    - Abbott & Costello, 1941 Apr.-June (Film-reel 203)
    - Alec Templeton, 1946 June-Aug. (Film-reel 310)
      Summer substitute for Edgar Bergen
    - Alex Templeton, 1947 June-Aug. (Film-reel 361)
    - Commercials, 1947 (Film-reel 360)
    - Don Ameche, 1942 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 203)
    - E Award program, 1943 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 203)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1944 Jan.-June (Film-reel 239)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 240)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1945 (Film-reel 279)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1946 (Film-reel 310)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1947 Jan.-May; Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 361)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1941 (Film-reel 202)
      No broadcasts July-Aug.
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1942 Jan.-May (Film-reel 202)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1942 May-Dec. (Film-reel 203)
      No broadcasts July-Aug. or Dec. 27
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 203)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1943 Dec. (Film-reel 204)
    - Francis Langford, 1945 June-Aug. (Film-reel 279)
    - Fred Allen, 1946 (Film-reel 310)
    - Gracie Fields, 1944 June-Aug. (Film-reel 239)
    - Paul Whiteman, 1943 June-Aug. (Film-reel 203)
    - Spot announcements, 1941; 1943 (Film-reel 202)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1946 June-Aug. (Film-reel 310)
      Summer substitute for Fred Allen
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1946 Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 311)
    - Commercials, 1937 (Film-reel 142)
    - Commercials, 1939 Jan.-July (Film-reel 148)
    - Commercials, 1939 July-Dec. (Film-reel 149)
    - Commercials, Canada, 1938 (Film-reel 143)
    - Commercials, coastal stations, 1938 (Film-reel 143)
    - Commercials, French network, 1938 (Film-reel 143)
    - Commercials--Philadelphia, Providence, Washington, 1938 May-Oct. (Film-reel 148)
    - Mrs. Annie Longworth Wallingford, 1936 Feb.-May (Film-reel 141)
    - Musical program, 1929 Sept.-1931 Jan. (Film-reel 84)
    - Orchestra, etc., 1933 Apr.-Sept.; 1934 May-Sept. (Film-reel 141)
  - Fleischmann's Royal, 1937-1945; 101
    - In the Dark, S. Eilers and N. Eddy, 1937 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 342)
    - Mary Marlin, 1945 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 280)
    - Mr. Jonas Changes His Mind, Edward Arnold, 1938 July 29 (Film-reel 342)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 342)
    - Spot announcements, 1945 July 31 (Film-reel 281)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast, 1930-1946; 102
    - Bakers of America, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 204)
    - Commercials, 1941 July-Aug. (Film-reel 168)
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-May (Film-reel 168)
    - Commercials--Canada, 1942 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 170)
    - Fleischmann's Yeast Hour, Baltimore, 1931 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 244)
      Missing Apr. 4, 11, 18, July 25
    - Rudy Vallee, 1930 Nov.-1931 Dec. (Film-reel 244)
    - 1945-1946 (Film-reel 737)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Bread, 1931-1938; 103
    - Great Moments in History, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 13)
    - Great Moments in History, 1933 (Film-reel 14)
    - Joe Penner, 1933 Oct.-1935 June (Film-reel 14)
    - Joe Penner, 1934 Dec.-1935 June (Film-reel 15)
    - Peg Murray, 1937 Oct.-1938 June (Film-reel 20)
    - Robert Ripley, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 20)
    - Three Bakers, 1932 (Film-reel 13)
    - Three Bakers, 1931 (Film-reel 140)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1930-1942; 104
    - All Colored Show, 1937 Apr.-June (Film-reel 16)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1937 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 15)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1937 Oct. (Film-reel 16)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1938 July-Dec. (Film-reel 16)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 17)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1939 (Film-reel 18)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1939 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 19)
    - Husbands and Wives, 1936 July-Sept. (Film-reel 15)
    - I Love a Mystery, 1939 (Film-reel 26)
    - I Love a Mystery, 1939 June-Dec. (Film-reel 27)
    - I Love a Mystery, 1939 Dec.-1942 (Film-reel 28)
    - Robert Ripley, 1935-1937 (Film-reel 19)
    - Royal Aspic/Vox Pop, 1935 July-Sept. (Film-reel 15)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1930-1932 July (Film-reel 20)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1932 July-1933 Aug. (Film-reel 21)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1933 Aug.-1934 (Film-reel 22)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1934 Aug.-1935 July (Film-reel 23)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1935 July-1936 Aug. (Film-reel 24)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1936 (Film-reel 25)
      Missing years 1937-1939; Edgar Bergen first appeared with Rudy Vallee on Dec. 17, 1936
    - Werner Jannsen, 1937 July-Sept. (Film-reel 16)
  - Magic Baking Powder (Canada) Commercials, 1933-1941; 105
    - 1933-1937 (Film-reel 30)
    - 1937 Feb.-1938 Jan. (Film-reel 31)
    - 1938 (Film-reel 141)
    - 1941 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 170)
  - Mary Marlin, 1943-1944; 106
    - Audition script, 1943 Sept. (Film-reel 204)
    - Royal Gelatine/Desserts, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 204)
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 204)
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, 1944 Jan.-May 5 (Film-reel 240)
      No broadcasts on June 6 (D Day), July 21
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, 1944 May-Nov. (Film-reel 241)
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, 1944 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 242)
  - One Man's Family, 1932-1949; 107
    - Radio histories, 1932-1949 (Film-reel 737)
    - Sales Meeting record, 1941 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 168)
    - Script, 1942 Jan.-July (Film-reel 168)
    - 1937 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 141)
    - 1937 Mar.-1938 Mar. (Film-reel 142)
    - 1938 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 143)
    - 1938 Dec. (Film-reel 148)
    - 1939 (Film-reel 148)
    - 1939 (Film-reel 149)
    - 1935 Mar.-1936 June (Film-reel 165)
    - 1936 June-Dec., 1940 Jan.-July (Film-reel 166)
    - 1941 Jan.-July (Film-reel 167)
    - 1940 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 167)
    - 1942 July-Aug. (Film-reel 168)
    - 1941 July-Dec. (Film-reel 168)
    - 1945 Jan.-June (Film-reel 280)
    - 1945 June-Dec. (Film-reel 281)
    - 1946 (Film-reel 309)
    - 1940s (Film-reel 343)
    - 1947 (Film-reel 359)
    - 1947 (Film-reel 360)
    - 1947 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 361)
    - 1949 (Film-reel 733)
  - Other Programming, 1928-1949; 108
    - Baking industry program, 1931 Oct. (Film-reel 31)
    - Beny Kreuger & Orchestra--Georgie Price, 1932 May 19 (Film-reel 89)
    - Beny Kreuger & Orchestra--Georgie Price, 1932 June-Dec. (Film-reel 90)
    - Bergen Shaw, Open Door radio histories, coffee spots, 1928-1949 (Film-reel 737)
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Nov. (Film-reel 359)
    - Commercials, 1947 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 360)
    - Commercials, 1947 (Film-reel 360)
    - Fleischmann commercials, 1937-1940 (Film-reel 31)
      Including Spanish language commercials
    - Fleischmann's Food Talks, 1929 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 31)
    - Fleischmann's Vitamin Yeast tablets, 1944 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 215)
    - Fleischmann's yeast drink (Canada), 1940 Oct.-Nov.; 1941 Jan.-July (Film-reel 167)
    - Fred Allen Show, 1947 (Film-reel 360)
    - Fred Allen Show radio histories, 1945-1947 (Film-reel 737)
    - Hour Glass, Face to Face television histories, 1946-1949 (Film-reel 737)
    - Life and Love of Dr. Susan episode 129, 1939 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 31)
    - Mary Marlin, 1943 Sept.-1945 Apr. (Film-reel 262)
    - Mary Martin radio histories, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 737)
    - One Man's Family, 1949 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 733)
    - Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 June-Aug. (Film-reel 717)
    - Royal puddings, 1942 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 168)
    - Royal tapioca pudding, 1940 Nov.-1941 Jan. (Film-reel 167)
    - Royal tapioca pudding, 1941 Aug. (Film-reel 168)
    - Royal yeast cakes (Canada), 1934 Feb.-Sept. (Film-reel 31)
    - Spot announcements, 1945 Oct.-1946 Feb. (Film-reel 309)
    - William L. Shirer News, 1947 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 365)
  - Royal Baking Powder, 1928-1941; 109
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb. (Film-reel 167)
    - Martha Deane, 1937 May-Nov. (Film-reel 30)
    - Martha Deane commercials, 1936 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 31)
    - Talks--Pacific Coast, 1928 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 31)
  - Royal Desserts, 1932-1939; 110
    - Commercials, 1932 Jan.-July (Film-reel 31)
    - Commercials, 1932 July-Dec. (Film-reel 32)
    - Commercials, 1933-1934 (Film-reel 140)
    - Frank Fay, 1936 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 32)
    - I Love a Mystery, 1939 (Film-reel 26)
    - Mary Pickford, 1935 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 140)
    - Those We Love, 1939 Oct.-1940 Mar. (Film-reel 30)
  - Royal Gelatine, 1931-1945; 111
    - Audition, 1931 (Film-reel 31)
    - Auditions, Beatrice Lillie, 1945 (Film-reel 343)
    - Martha Deane commercials, 1936 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 31)
    - Script, 1942 July-Aug. (Film-reel 168)
    - Spot announcements, KFBB, 1941 Dec.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 244)
    - 1941 June (Film-reel 167)
  - Rubinoff & Orchestra, 1931-1940; 112
    - A.L. Alexander--Good Will Court, 1936 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 93)
    - A.L. Alexander--Good Will Court, 1936 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 93)
    - Burns & Allen, 1932 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 89)
    - Commercials, 1934 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 92)
    - Commercials, 1936 (Film-reel 93)
    - Commercials, 1937 (Film-reel 94)
    - Commercials, 1938 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 95)
    - Commercials, 1938 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 96)
    - Commercials, 1939 July (Film-reel 96)
    - Commercials, 1939 Jan.-June (Film-reel 97)
    - Commercials, 1939 June-Dec. (Film-reel 98)
    - Commercials, 1940 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 98)
    - Commercials, 1940 (Film-reel 99)
      (Off air July-August)
    - Commercials, 1939 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 99)
    - Commercials, 1939-1940 (Film-reel 100)
    - Commercials (Canada), 1937 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 94)
    - Commercials (Canada), 1938 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 96)
    - Commercials (French network), 1938 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 96)
    - Commercials (French network), 1939 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 98)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1931 July-1932 Jan. (Film-reel 84)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1932 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 89)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1933 (Film-reel 90)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1934 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 91)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1934 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 92)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1937 May-Oct. (Film-reel 93)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1938 Jan.-May (Film-reel 94)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1939 Jan.-July (Film-reel 96)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1939 July-Dec. (Film-reel 97)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1940 (Film-reel 98)
      Off air July-August
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1940 (Film-reel 99)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1937 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 94)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1938 May-Dec. (Film-reel 95)
    - George Jessel, 1932 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 84)
    - George Jessel, 1932 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 89)
    - Georgie Price, 1932 Aug. 7 (Film-reel 89)
    - Georgie Price and the Revelers, 1932 sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 89)
    - Harry Richman, 1932 May-Sept. (Film-reel 89)
    - Haven MacQuarrie--Do You Want To Be an Actor?, 1936 Dec. (Film-reel 93)
    - Haven MacQuarrie--Do You Want To Be an Actor?, 1937 Jan.-May (Film-reel 93)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1933 Sept. (Film-reel 90)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1934 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 91)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1933 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 91)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1934 Sept. (Film-reel 92)
    - Major Bowes, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 92)
    - Major Bowes, 1936 May-Sept. (Film-reel 93)
    - Maurice Chevalier, 1931 Feb.-June (Film-reel 84)
    - Musical program (coastal stations), 1931 Jan.-1932 Apr. (Film-reel 84)
    - Opera Series, 1934 Dec. (Film-reel 92)
    - Opera Series, 1935 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 92)
    - Sims & Bailey, 1933 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 90)
      Bert Lahr and cast
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Mar.-Sept. (Film-reel 99)
    - Springtime & Harvest, 1939-1940 (Film-reel 99)
      Several episodes missing
    - Springtime & Harvest, 1939 Oct.-1940 June (Film-reel 100)
  - Television Programming, 1946-1947; 113
    - Dancing on Air, 1947 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 365)
    - Face to Face, 1947 Jan. (Film-reel 365)
    - Face to Face, commercials, 1946 June-Dec. (Film-reel 311)
    - Hour Glass, 1946 May-Dec. (Film-reel 311)
      No broadcast Sept. 26, Nov. 21
    - Hour Glass, 1947 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 365)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1940-1956; 114
    - Canada, 1941 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 168)
    - Canada Vass Family, 1940 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 168)
    - Canada Vass Family, 1941 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 168)
    - Commercials, 1942 Sept. 6 (Film-reel 168)
    - Fred Allen, 1945 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 279)
    - Fred Allen, 1945 Dec. (Film-reel 280)
    - Great Falls Mont. one-minute announcement, 1941 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 168)
    - I Love a Mystery, 1941 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 168)
    - Spot announcements, 1941 Jan. (Film-reel 279)
    - Spot announcements, KFBB, 1941 Oct.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 244)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1945 June-Sept. (Film-reel 279)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1945 June 10 (Film-reel 343)
    - Valiant Lady, 1956 June-Aug. (Film-reel 1007)
    - 1942 July-Aug. (Film-reel 168)
- Swift & Co., 1931-1955; 47
  - Programming, 1931-1955; 115
    - Garry Moore Show, 1955 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 992)
    - Movie Time, 1952 Jan. (Film-reel 915)
    - Program, 1936 Jan.-May (Film-reel 139)
    - Program, 1936 May-June (Film-reel 140)
    - Salesmen conference commercials, 1948 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 418)
    - Sigmund Romberg, William Lyon Phelps, 1934 Oct.-1935 Apr. (Film-reel 119)
    - The Formay Program (Miss Lucy Allen)--Happy Ramblers, 1932 Oct.-1934 Apr. (Film-reel 119)
    - The Garden Hour, 1931 Feb.-May; 1932 Jan.-May (Film-reel 115)
  - Stebbins Boys, 1931-1932; 116
    - 1931 July-Aug. (Film-reel 115)
    - 1931 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 116)
    - 1931 Dec.-1932 May (Film-reel 117)
    - 1932 May-Oct. (Film-reel 118)
  - Swift's Movie Time, 1951-1952; 117
    - 1951 Oct.-Nov. 2 (Film-reel 795)
    - 1951 Nov. 2-Dec. (Film-reel 796)
    - 1951 Oct.-1952 Jan. (Film-reel 1006)
    - Commercials, approximately 1951 (Film-reel 1007)
- Sylvania, 1955-1956; 48
  - Beat the Clock, 1955-1956; 118
    - Atlantic City, approximately 1955 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Commercials, 1956 Mar. 10-June 16 (Film-reel 1011)
      Mar. 10 broadcast International Show; Mar. 31 broadcast April Fool's Show
    - Commercials, 1955 Sept. 24-1956 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 1011)
      Feb. 11 broadcast Gay '90s Show
    - 1955 (Film-reel 992)
    - 1956 Jan.-June (Film-reel 1007)
    - 1956 May 3 (Film-reel 1011)